export default data = [
  {
    question: "What is the IPA transcription for the word 'pizza'?",
    options: ["/piːtsə/", "/pɪtsə/", "/pizə/", "/piːzə/"],
    correct_option: "/pizə/",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the IPA transcription for the word 'shower'?",
    options: ["/ʃaʊər/", "/ʃaʊr/", "/ʃɔːr/", "/ʃoʊər/"],
    correct_option: "/ʃaʊər/",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the IPA transcription for the word 'lion'?",
    options: ["/laɪən/", "/liːən/", "/laɪɑn/", "/liːɑn/"],
    correct_option: "/liːən/",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the IPA transcription for the word 'train'?",
    options: ["/treɪn/", "/truɪn/", "/treən/", "/traɪn/"],
    correct_option: "/treɪn/",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the IPA transcription for the word 'baggage'?",
    options: ["/bæɡɪdʒ/", "/bæɡeɪdʒ/", "/bəɡædʒ/", "/bəɡeɪdʒ/"],
    correct_option: "/bæɡeɪdʒ/",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the IPA transcription for the word 'beauty'?",
    options: ["/bjuti/", "/bjuːti/", "/buti/", "/buːti/"],
    correct_option: "/bjuːti/",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the IPA transcription for the word 'duck'?",
    options: ["/dʌk/", "/dɑk/", "/dʊk/", "/dək/"],
    correct_option: "/dʌk/",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the IPA transcription for the word 'window'?",
    options: ["/wɪndoʊ/", "/wɪndəʊ/", "/wɪndo/", "/wɪndɑ/"],
    correct_option: "/wɪndəʊ/",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the IPA transcription for the word 'thought'?",
    options: ["/θɔt/", "/θoʊt/", "/θɑt/", "/θʌt/"],
    correct_option: "/θoʊt/",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the IPA transcription for the word 'jealous'?",
    options: ["/dʒɛləs/", "/dʒɛlʌs/", "/dʒeləs/", "/dʒelʌs/"],
    correct_option: "/dʒɛləs/",
  },
];
